business-mortgage.ltd 2018-05-10

# Privacy Policy – Business Mortgage

Business mortgage cares about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following terms to learn more about our privacy policy. By registering to and creating account at Business mortgage.tv you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

We will never sell your personal information, or use it for any other purpose other than logging in/out, demographics for our knowledge, and any voluntary feature of the site.  
We use cookies with minimal information in them.  
We use Google Analytics, which is covered by Google’s Privacy policy  
We allow you to contact other members via profile pages, but no private information is sent unless you want them to see. (you can choose not receive any communication from anyone.)

If you are below 13 then you can NOT use this forum. Do NOT register if you are below the age of 13.  
Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.  
Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings. (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting aboutads.info.)

If you have not opted out of third-party ad serving, the cookies of other third-party vendors or ad networks may also be used to serve ads on your site, and should be disclosed in your privacy policy as well in the following manner.

Notify your site visitors of the third-party vendors and ad networks serving ads on your site.  
Provide links to the appropriate vendor and ad network websites.  
Inform your users that they may visit those websites to opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of some third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting aboutads.info.

Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we’re unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the Network Advertising Initiative for guidance on drafting a privacy policy.

In detail

What does Business mortgage Privacy Policy cover?  
All the personal information we collect is noted on your profile page. That includes your name, email, date of birth and biographic information. Thepersonal information that you provide is used for Registration purpose. In order for you to participate in Business mortgage discussion you must complete a registration form. As part of registration form, we require your email address.  
Profile Information  
Business mortgage allow other users to browse your full name, instant messaging URL, and other details within your member profile should you provide this optional information. Business mortgage allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the website.  
Cookies  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser in order to check in if you are logged in or out. All the other information is located in Business mortgage server. Some of our business partners may use cookies on our website (for example advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.  
Third-party Advertisement  
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.  
Membership Validity  
We reserve the right to delete any message, ban any member for any or no reason whatsoever. Members found to be abusing the contact form, using it for commercial purposes, or otherwise breaking the Community Guidelines will have his/her membership suspended.  
Children below 13 DO NOT Register  
The Federal Trade Commission’s Children Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) require that Web Sites are to obtain parental consent before collecting, using, or disclosing personal information from children under 13. If you are below 13 then you cannot use this forum. Do NOT register if you are below the age of 13.
